Lincy Ellermeijer

02/06/1995

Contact information



De Grote Wielen 19 - 1187LH - Amstelveen - The Netherlands +31622415548 lincyellermeijer@gmail.com lincyellermeijer.github.io nl.linkedin.com/in/lincyellermeijer

PROFILE

I'm in my fourth and last year of the study Game Development. I enjoy this study very much and have acquired knowledge and experience in different programming languages, methods and techniques. In projects I work very well in a team, but I can also work good independently. I want to expand my knowledge and experience and develop myself further as a good Game Developer.

EDUCATION

Amsterdam University of Applied Sciences 2014-2018 | Achieved Propaedeutic HBO-ICT - Game Development

Hochschule der Medien, Stuttgart, Germany 2017-2017 | Successfully completed with high grades Minor Game Technology

Keizer Karel College, Amstelveen 2007-2013 | Achieved Certificate of Secondary Education VWO - E&M and C&M (Economy, Culture and Society)

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

Bright IT Students | Part of the team February 2016 – To date, Amsterdam, The Netherlands

GAMEDIA | Intern Game Developer September 2016 – January 2017, Alkmaar, The Netherlands

Microsoft | Internship Mobile Development February 2016 – July 2016, Schiphol, The Netherlands

SKILLS

Knows multiple programming languages (s.a. C#, Java, HTML) and
other IT knowledge (s.a. Unity, Unreal, Visual Studio, GIT, Scrum)
Quick learner, adapts easily
Creative and spontaneous